<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Charitable</string>
    <string name="mainTitle">Feeling Charitable?</string>
    <string name="btnDonate">Donate</string>
    <string name="btnAmount">See Donation Amount</string>
    <string name="txtCharity1">Doctors Without Borders</string>
    <string name="txtCharity2">Charity 2</string>
    <string name="txtCharity3">Charity 3</string>
    <string name="txtCharity4">Charity 4</string>
    <string-array name="charityArray">
        <item>Doctors Without Borders</item>
        <item>St. Jude Children\'s Research Hospital</item>
        <item>Child\'s Play</item>
        <item>Trevor Project</item>
        <item>American Red Cross</item>
        <item>Salvation Army</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="txtSummary1"></string>

    <string-array name="txtSummary">
        <item>An independent, global movement providing medical aid where it\’s needed most.
    Doctors Without Borders, is an international humanitarian medical non-governmental organisation (NGO)
        of French origin best known for its projects in conflict zones and in countries affected by endemic diseases</item>
        <item>
            The mission of St. Jude Children\’s Research Hospital is to advance cures,
            and means of prevention, for pediatric catastrophic diseases through research and treatment.
            Consistent with the vision of our founder Danny Thomas, no child is denied treatment based on race,
            religion or a family\'s ability to pay.
        </item>
        <item>
            Child\’s Play, a game industry charity dedicated to improving the lives of children with toys and games in our network of over 100 hospitals worldwide.
            Over the years, you as a community have answered the call and come together to raise millions of dollars.
            Child’s Play works in two ways. With the help of hospital staff, we set up gift wish lists full of video games,
            toys, books, and other fun stuff for kids. By clicking on a hospital location on our map, you can view that hospital’s wish list and send a gift.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Trevor Project is an American non-profit organization
            founded in 1998 focused on suicide prevention efforts among lesbian, gay,
            bisexual, transgender, and questioning youth. Through a toll-free telephone number,
            it operates The Trevor Lifeline,
            a confidential service that offers trained counselors.
        </item>
        <item>
            The American Red Cross, also known as The American National Red Cross, is a humanitarian organization that provides emergency assistance, disaster relief,
            and disaster preparedness education in the United States.
            The American Red Cross prevents and alleviates human suffering in the face of emergencies by mobilizing the power of volunteers and the generosity of donors.​
        </item>
        <item>
             The Salvation Army, an international movement, is an evangelical part of the universal Christian Church.
            Its message is based on the Bible.
            Its ministry is motivated by the love of God.
            Its mission is to preach the gospel of Jesus Christ and to meet human needs in His name without discrimination.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="urlPages">
        <item>https://donate.doctorswithoutborders.org/onetime.cfm</item>
        <item>https://www.stjude.org/donate/donate-to-st-jude.html?sc_icid=wtg-mm-btn-donate-now</item>
        <item>https://www.childsplaycharity.org/donate</item>
        <item>https://give.thetrevorproject.org/give/63307/#!/donation/checkout</item>
        <item>https://www.redcross.org/donate/donation.html/</item>
        <item>https://www.salvationarmyusa.org/usn/</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>
